import { Question } from "./Interfaces";

const Questions: Array<Question> = [
  { Question: "What is Kelly's middle name?", Answer: "Nicolle", WrongAnswers: ["Noelle", "Mary", "Marie"] },
  { Question: "What year was Kelly born?", Answer: "2002", WrongAnswers: ["2003", "2001", "2010"] },
  { Question: "What is Kelly allergic to?", Answer: "Tree nuts", WrongAnswers: ["Peanuts", "Chocolate", "Dairy"] },
  { Question: "In what month was Kelly born?", Answer: "December", WrongAnswers: ["November", "August", "January"] },
  { Question: "What day of the month was Kelly born?", Answer: "9th", WrongAnswers: ["18th", "28th", "12th"] },
  {
    Question: "What does Kelly want to study in college?",
    Answer: "Elementary Education",
    WrongAnswers: ["Programming", "Robotics", "English"],
  },
  {
    Question: "What is Kelly's favorite TV series?",
    Answer: "Friends",
    WrongAnswers: ["Brooklyn 99", "How I Met Your Mother", "Grey's Anatomy"],
  },
  {
    Question: "What job does Kelly have?",
    Answer: "Babysitting / Nanny",
    WrongAnswers: ["AMC", "Target", "Chipotle"],
  },
  { Question: "What is Kelly's favorite color?", Answer: "Blue", WrongAnswers: ["Green", "Pink", "Purple"] },
  { Question: "What is Kelly's favorite candy?", Answer: "Reeses", WrongAnswers: ["Hershey", "M&Ms", "Snickers"] },
  {
    Question: "What is Kelly's favorite fast casual restaurant?",
    Answer: "Chipotle",
    WrongAnswers: ["Noodles & Company", "Cafe Zupas", "Panera"],
  },
  {
    Question: "What pop does Kelly like to drink?",
    Answer: "Dr. Pepper / Dr. Thunder",
    WrongAnswers: ["Mountain Dew / Mountain Lightning", "Sprite / 7 Up / Twist Up", "No caffeine for Kelly!"],
  },
  {
    Question: "What international city would Kelly most like to travel to?",
    Answer: "Paris, France",
    WrongAnswers: ["London, England", "Madrid, Spain", "Galway, Ireland"],
  },
  {
    Question: "What school will Kelly be attending in the fall?",
    Answer: "University of Wisconsin River Falls",
    WrongAnswers: ["University of Saint Thomas", "Saint Scholastica", "University of Wisconsin Eau Claire"],
  },
  {
    Question: "Which extra cirricular activity did Kelly NOT participate in during high school?",
    Answer: "Costumes",
    WrongAnswers: ["Robotics", "Speech", "Drone Racing"],
  },
  
  { Question: "What is Kelly's favorite subject?", Answer: "English", WrongAnswers: ["Spanish", "Physics", "Math"] },
  {
    Question: "What is Kelly's least favorite subject?",
    Answer: "Math",
    WrongAnswers: ["English", "Religion", "History"],
  },
  {
    Question: `Kelly is not a "strawberry blonde" but a what?`,
    Answer: "blueberry blonde",
    WrongAnswers: ["raspberry blonde", "blackberry blonde", "canteloupe blonde"],
  },
  {
    Question: "What is Kelly's favorite nick name for Everest?",
    Answer: "My Bubby",
    WrongAnswers: ["Pupper", "Puppy", "Ev"],
  },
  {
    Question: "What is Kelly's favorite type of popcorn?",
    Answer: "White Cheddar (Aldi's)",
    WrongAnswers: ["Microwave Popcorn", "Puffcorn", "Plain Popcorn"],
  },
  {
    Question: "What is Kelly's favorite dessert?",
    Answer: "Wonder bars",
    WrongAnswers: ["Brownies", "Cookie bars", "Cake pops"],
  },
  { Question: "What is Kelly's favorite meal?", Answer: "Parmesan Crusted Chicken", WrongAnswers: ["Chicken Tenders", "Lasagna", "Stuffed Green Peppers"] },
  {
    Question: "What is Kelly's favorite Disney movie?",
    Answer: "Cinderella",
    WrongAnswers: ["The Little Mermaid", "Tangled", "Frozen"],
  },
  {
    Question: "What is Kelly's favorite Disney character?",
    Answer: "Mickey Mouse",
    WrongAnswers: ["Minnie Mouse", "Donald Duck", "Daisy Duck"],
  },
  {
    Question: "Which are Kelly's favorite Disney princesses?",
    Answer: "Cinderella and Jasmine",
    WrongAnswers: ["Cinderella and Ariel", "Jasmine and Ariel", "Cinderella and Elsa"],
  },
  { Question: "What instrument does Kelly play?", Answer: "Flute", WrongAnswers: ["Trombone", "Piano", "Piccolo"] },
  {
    Question: "How many years has Kelly participated in band?",
    Answer: "8",
    WrongAnswers: ["7", "6", "9"],
  },
  {
    Question: "What does Kelly volunteer for on Sundays?",
    Answer: "Sunday School",
    WrongAnswers: ["FMSC", "Partnership Academy", "ARC Value Village"],
  },
];

export default Questions;
